Not much has changed at Hogwarts since last year.
Only Kim fell off the ladder
during her part-time job in Hrochoť
and impaled her throat directly on the rake.
During a difficult operation,
which lasted 260 hours
they miraculously managed to eliminate her retardation.
But her vocal cords will be damaged for life.
Professor Ľudo Kolman,
under the threat of extermination of all Jews
converted to Islam
and Mr. Pipík was replaced by one distinguished professor.
A very interesting year at Hogwarts was awaiting for Dano Drevo.
See for yourself.
Štúdio POG presents:
Dano Drevo and the Tournament of Meky Žbirka
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.32,0:01:27.20,Default,,0,0,0,,
(Dear listeners, greetings to all who like good music,)
(Hello from DJ László from Európa 2!)
[Alma a fa alatt]
♪ (Apple under the tree, summer red apple.) ♪
♪ (My lover's mother insults me.) ♪
♪ (She insults me, she gossips about me.) ♪
(I love your daughter, I can't help it.)
[Miro Žbirka - 22 dní]
Although it is true that even shit looks better than you,
but we'll figure something out about that.
Ancient Jewish medicine could help you -
to paint your face, every day
with vaginal discharge,
it doesn't look that bad at all.
Mr. Žbirka, don't worry, we'll figure something out.
Give it time and the skin will regenerate.
Time heals all wounds, Mr. Žbirka,
I know what I'm talking about.
I'm curious how will I in this shape (...) Slávik.
I still can't understand it,
How could you fucking fall into a bath of acid in Patince?
I just lost my balance.
But looks don't matter,
you still have gold in your throat.
Shut up, Patkaň!
Mr. Žbirka, I have a great idea:
yesterday I got so fucking wasted,
I puked over myself.
Jerguš, to the point!
Okay, okay,
What if we did a tournament at Hogwarts?
What tournament?
It's obvious you need a new face
well, and there are young and beautiful students at Hogwarts.
You will organize a tournament under the guise of a big win
and in the end you will take the face of the fittest handsome person.
It's a vile and insidious plan.
That's not a bad idea at all, Jerguš.
It would even solve my wart problems.
And now invite the old man outside for coffee.
Actually, no.
I'd rather waste him.
Dano! Dano, get up! Get up.
Come on, he shit himself...
Dano! Get up.
Kim, I thought
that Ibrahim Maiga is waking me up.
Dano, stop it.
You know I'm sensitive to my voice.
Peder. Peder!
You monster!
I am a monster to you, you bastard?
I, who does community service,
I sweep the sidewalks.
So I am a monster for that red dickhead.
What have I lived to see,
he sleeps until lunch,
I will kill him with an ashtray.
Wow, I'm so looking forward to the egg-throwing race.
Now we will meet Mr. Fekete and his son Šaňko.
I'm warning you kids, they are Olaš Gypsies,
so don't give them anything.
Besides, Šaňko is extremely vulgar,
so ignore him.
Oh, you tramps.
You are half an hour late.
Why did your cow's udders dry up?
They didn't dry up, they didn't dry up,
but this fellow had difficult dreams,
so he pooped his pajamas.
And so we changed his diapers until everything was in order.
Nice to see you, you brownie.
Hello Šaňko, do you remember me?
Remember you?
I usually don't remember redheaded assholes.
Well, well, Šaňo.
Listen, aren't you Dano Drevo?
That Dano Drevo who always shits himself.
Yes, that's me.
Nice to meet you, Fekete.
Could you lend me five euros, Danko?
Well, I'll take a look.
Excellent, son.
[Johnny Cash - I've Been Everywhere]
Children, there should be this old shoe somewhere here,
so try to find it.
Father, father, there's a shoe here.
Father!
I found the shoe!
Father, come here, come here!
I found that shoe!
Father!
Fine Ctiborko, shut up already.
So: northeast wind,
Dano shat himself at 10:37,
so it's going to work now.
Dano, you are such a swine!
You're a terrible swine, really.
Children, do you know what a gypsy carousel is?
Get ready.
Dano!
[Flo Rida - Right Round]
Children, let go!
Let go, now!
[Эдуа́рд Хиль - Я о́чень рад, ведь я, наконе́ц, возвраща́юсь домо́й]
Oh, you stupid children.
They always fall for it.
Get up, you wooden cocksucker.
Thank you.
Look, a real black person!
Miro, fuck him up!
Alright, so I'll return the 120 euros maybe...
I don't know when.
Bye, you Gypsy.
Bye.
Come Šaňko, come quickly.
Maroš, you dick!
Redheaded pigs have the right of way.
Dano, welcome to the tent of love.
[The Irish Rovers - Drunken Sailor]
So on this couch we conceived Ctibor,
on that one Peder.
Down here we made the twins,
I don't know what their names are.
On this table I usually jerk off.
Ew, dad!
Well, and that's it.
So Dano, feel at home here.
You stud.
Coming next, with their dance performance
slaves from Ivory Coast!
Well, what is this scum doing here?
Do you know who's going to sing today?
Meky Žbirka was unable to attend.
So they chose me.
Dad ran away from his alcohol therapy because of this.
He even ran naked across Košice.
Stano, stop it, don't embarrass me.
Well, Drevo, how is Old Jano?
What a blond dickhead, let's get out of here.
Try to keep your undies clean today, Drevo.
Poop!
Please welcome the team of
the wasted Irish!
The Irish are playing today without their captain John McGrady,
who barfed like a pig this morning.
And now a big round of applause for the Hungarian team
from Streda nad Bodrogom!
[PKO, AZA - Szövetség]
♪ (Sex, drugs, weed, that is what we need.) ♪
♪ (Just a few faggot YouTubers we'll stick in our pockets.) ♪
♪ (Why do you need to talk shit with your brain, I don't want to talk shit anyway.) ♪
Look, that's the best player in the world!
♪ (I'm fucking the music, I want to dissolve.) ♪
The Hungarian team will be led by no one else,
♪ (It doesn't matter how big of a gangster you are, you're a liar.) ♪
like the great Gábor the Tailed One himself!
♪ (Why should I keep my distance, why should I worry.) ♪
♪ (One call and you're first to suck out my cum.) ♪
♪ (You started it, but I have the last word.) ♪
Gábor! Gábor!
♪ (I'm gonna be the one who will open your Christmas gift.) ♪
♪ (Because you don't create culture) ♪
Gábor! Gábor!
♪ (and you'll see that this will be your loss) ♪
♪ (My opinions are not in line with any principles.) ♪
Jožo!
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
the World Egg Throwing Championships.
I would like to point out,
that I suffer from Alzheimer's disease.
When my mother cooked plum dumplings for me as a child,
I shoved a few up my ass.
Therefore, consider this tournament
as officially
commenced!
[Europe - The Final Countdown]
Gábor, he is our star,
his tail looks like a viper.
He always drives us forward,
he hides a surprise in his pants.
Gábor, Gábor, Gábor, Gábor,
He is the best!
Gábor, Gábor.
He is number one!
It is said that during childbirth, the doctor
could not determine what is the umbilical cord
and what is the penis!
Gábor, Gábor, Gábor, Gábor!
His anaconda is otherworldly!
You'd enjoy that in your ass, Peder!
Peder has fallen in love!
For Gábor...
Peter loves Gábor.
You'd like his tail in your anal, right?
But Gábor doesn't want Peter.
You're a motherfucker.
How dare you, you red-haired son of a bitch?
Stop it, stop it, you scoundrels!
Some Gypsies must have set fire to the camp.
Ctibor, take my pills and let's go.
If I don't survive,
give my property to the Jehovah's Witnesses.
And let Ctibor become the head of the family.
Dano!
Fuck, where's my toothpick?
Ku Klux Klan! Ku Klux Klan!
Ku Klux Klan!
Maroš, let it go!
Dano!
Where's my prosthesis? Fuck...
Don't touch my son, you old jerk!
Sorry, madam, sorry.
Drevo is on the ground,
Kick him in the noggin someone, quickly.
Kick him already, fuck!
I like the shade of apple trees, the right people.
I like it when the alarm doesn't ring in the morning.
I know,
I carry that gene in me.
No crises,
my brother.
Take it easy (easy),
all right.
[Miro Žbirka - Balada o poľných vtákoch]
Well, well, who do I see in the distance?
Show yourself, boy.
Don't you have a beautiful face,
do not run away from me behind that little sheet.
Don't hide from me, you handsome guy.
Dano.
I'll find you, handsome guy.
Dano. Dano. Danö!
Dano, are you okay?
Your head got puffed-up.
Kill those cockroaches!
Fucking capitalists.
Get out of the way, you communist.
Whose rotten
imperialist hands
started this fire?
Have you gone completely crazy?
Comrades, which one of you was it?
Where are your pioneer scarves?
What scarves?
What are you rambling about?
But I don't have a scarf.
Dano, he's a die-hard Bolshevik.
Look at those eyebrows.
Dude, pure Brezhnev.
Where?
I remember.
Someone kicked me to the ground.
Do you know who it was?
I saw them, he had a mustache and a hat.
We're leaving.
You fucking Jewish Bolshevik!
Dasvidania, assholes.
Dano, forget him.
But I would like to know why is that skull in the sky.
It reminds me of the new album cover
of the ageless Miro Žbirka.
[Maxim Turbulenc - Jede jede mašinka]
The food cart is coming,
Tuck your dicks away!
Well, so you don't want anything,
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
Wait, you old shag!
Give me:
Alpa,
window cleaner...
three bread rolls with cod.
And these cigarettes.
Peter, you smoke?
I don't, that's my afternoon snack.
Kung Pao.
Well, Kung Pao we don't have, you cross-eyed monster,
but here is some sushi.
To the gas chambers with these Easterners.
Are you going to eat something, you squinty fuck?
I've lost my appetite for food, thank you.
Well, that's fucked up,
so he doesn't want anything,
fucking children, I would shoot them all...
Dano, you pig, you cannot be serious.
To shit yourself in the compartment?
For real Dano, just when I started eating.
I will hurl into your lap.
Then it will rot and I'll hurl again.
Dano, try to do something with it.
Kim, but I'm fine.
Dano, yesterday I saw an advertisement for a medicine.
It's some activated charcoal called Sirius Black.
Helps with digestive problems.
Please Dano, order it today,
ideally right now.
[The Kooks - Seaside]
Get outta here you...
fat duck.
[Marks Orchesta - Stars Of Tomorrow]
Wow, that's beautiful.
It's a godsend!
That's incredible.
Don't cover it, I can't see!
Unreal.
Beautiful.
This is so fucked up.
What an experience.
Bread spread from shit for free!
Really?
No, hahahaha!
I wish you don't live to see tomorrow.
To the left, left, you fucking horses.
Someone take a picture of this!
Look, how he ate shit.
...they have to write down.
Ceremonial welcoming of first-year students
will take place tomorrow at my apartment.
In addition, Hogwarts will host
one very important tournament,
who is organized by...
What do you want now, Ambróz?
I've already done two laps around the school.
Do you think I'll win gold in 100 meters?
For sure, for sure, you've got what it takes,
Really? Alright.
Do two more laps, keep going.
Run Forrest, run!
And wash yourself!
The tournament organizer is
megastar Meky Žbirka.
Damn, that's sick.
They can't be serious.
That is pleasing.
...the one with the wart.
When Meky contacted me, I was initially hesitant,
if I should offer him this school for the tournament?
But, only one photo
of Peter Nagy without a wig -
naked Peter Nagy without a wig -
convinced me that the tournament will be here.
Meky has also requested
the highest possible number of beautiful contestants.
That is why I've invited the whores.
They are hygienic whores from the French village of Chevance.
Please welcome them together with their pimp.
Madam Brigite de Fecalie!
[K.Maro - Femme Like U]
Peder, look, she apparently secretly drinks urine.
Show me your pussy!
At least one boobie!
We want to see the coochie!
Maroš, are you jacking off?
I'm a faggot though.
Quiet, shh! Quiet.
And now the highlight of the evening, at least for me.
Welcome students from
the industrial trade school in Streda nad Bodrogom!
[Virrasztók - A Kaszás]
♪ (Death walks with a scythe, it finds everyone.) ♪
♪ (It shows its strength, waves his scythe,) ♪
♪ (nothing is sharper, no one is faster.) ♪
♪ (It doesn't care about flowers, cuts them off like weeds.) ♪
That's Gábor!
That is Gábor. Gábor. Gábor!
Gábor! I am your biggest fan!
Gábor, look here, I am here!
Gábor! Gábor!
Why don't you pay any attention to me, Gábor?
Hello János, faggot power.
Hello István,
I woudln't have thought of you as such scum.
You smell beautiful, you playboy.
Light showers apparently...
Fuck the weather girls.
Old Jano, I hope you know,
that I have very special dietary requirements.
I know that, Brigita.
Mr. Poslušný is a similar pig as you,
you will definitely take a liking to each other.
Once you need to try my specialty,
septic tank ferret.
You dickhead!
Have you completely fucking lost it, you dickhead?!
Alright, get out of here, you lowlife, get out.
Thank you, Ambróz.
Give them two euros for a beer later.
So, how do I start?
I'm already an old man,
but with a small boy's buttocks-
Old Jano!
What now, Ambróz?
You're supposed to be talking about the tournament.
Oh.
Sorry, sorry.
The main prize is Žbirka's signature,
the book We're Making Jam at our Cottage House
and 10,000 forints.
Sick.
However, this enviable prize will only be won by the only one
who can pass three challenging disciplines.
And now the main tournament coordinator Vasil
will announce one particularly important piece of information,
which for-
[Slovenské mamičky]
[Kopala studienku]
Isn't that the racist teacher by any chance?
What?
Dano,
he was fired five years ago.
Apparently an Indian student wished him good morning.
and for that, he put him in a microwave.
And during his defense, he started screaming the Slovak anthem.
Welcome Jozef, what took you so long?
Well,
Hungarians.
As always.
What do you think, Dano, what is he guzzling?
Probably some Lidl trash.
An extensive survey of our socialist youth union
has revealed that redheads do not have souls.
For this reason, redheads
will not be able to participate in the tournament.
You Satan!
I will kill your entire family!
Take that asshole away! Take that asshole away!
Silence!
And what if only my dick hair is red?
Ctibor, turn around.
Jeez, you're an eyesore.
A bluish flame.
Anyone who wants to participate in the tournament,
will throw a piece of paper with his nickname into it
or with something which characterizes them.
Do not throw your names in it.
Meky will choose three people to compete.
Selection
will take place
here in a week.
[Justin Timberlake - Cry Me a River]
(Gábor will be the winner...)
Jozef Šlota.
That's my name.
When I'm getting pissed off by dumb brats,
I write nonsense on the board.
I am known for my hatred
especially towards...
Hungarians,
but also Asians, Roma, Indians
Polynesian, Hispanic
and black people.
You racist.
Today we will talk about the Černová tragedy,
which you were taught in history class
completely wrong!
It happened on the twenty-seventh of October, nineteen-
Professor?
What do you want?
Sorry to interrupt you,
but shouldn't we be going over the insidious-
No idiot rocker with long hair
won't tell me what to teach!
During the Černová tragedy
the Hungarians shot 1,500 Slovaks.
What if a similar massacre happens again?
Today or tomorrow!
This place is crawling with Hungarian spies!
I'm betting that even in this class
there is someone Hungarian!
(That's not true, only my mom-)
If I wasn't on probation,
you'd be lying in a pool of blood already!
Alright, little punks.
Let's do an oral exam.
Peder!
Yes?
Samo Chalupka - Mor ho!
Graded, first four strophes.
Eagles flying down from the Tatras,
Aiming towards...
Ondatras.
I'm fucking the grave of Kleopatra.
Well, you're a hopeless case.
That's an F like nothing.
It's lucky you don't talk back.
Like the rocker,
because I would have fucking smacked you.
Fuck, what a generation...
If I had a flamethrower,
I'd burn down the entire elementary school.
Illiterate brats.
Hi.
(Finally someone saw me and took me out of this container.)
(I thought I would be left here alone forever.)
Head of Mečiar.
Head of Tásler.
Hop!
What, black man,
you eat these in Uganda?
Are you sweating, fattie?
I can smell the grease all the way here.
What irony,
A gypsy woman laughing at a black man and a swine.
Look, redhead,
maybe you'll turn gray from fear
and will become eligible for the tournament signup!
And what are you laughing at,
do you think
that you're from a superior race,
you Aryan?
This is amazing,
being able to teach again.
How about we throw that cockroach out now?
(My head is a little dizzy...)
Do you hear that Finno-Ugric wail?
(No, no! Anywhere but the water!)
(I thought I was going to shit my pants...)
(This looks to be a funny lesson.)
(Full of nonsense and goofing around.)
(I wonder what else awaits me.)
This insect was captured
near Komárno
and therefore he is Hungarian.
Through detailed analysis, I've found out
that he is the reincarnation
of the Hungarian gendarme
Ferencz Fereszlanyi,
who has in Černová
killed over 100 Slovaks.
Who here in the class feels national pride?
So who do we choose?
Toothie.
I mean... sorry.
Bubák.
Bubák, stand up.
Jesus Christ, your mouth smells
as if a homeless person had just thrown up in there,
one who's been eating his own shit.
Well, because...
my gums are rotting.
That's exactly what I thought!
Come here, come here.
Phew, fuck...
So let's try the first insidious spell.
Torture.
(That hurts so much! Stop it, you stupid fascist!)
(I'll tell all of this to my mosquito friend from Balaton, he'll bite him real bad!)
(When will this suffering end?!)
(I cannot die this young, I'm so handsome and there are horror movie roles waiting for me!)
Stop it!
You wrinkled dickhead!
(I'll be better, I'll be better, just stop torturing me!)
(Thank you very much for freeing me from that endless torment.)
So, a wrinkled dickhead?
(Where are you going?)
(Why are we walking to that rock singer?)
(Shall we listen to some rock?)
(I would love something by Bon Jovi.)
Since you have so much to say,
you ill-mannered hippie.
You should cast the most insidious of spells.
Say those two words of death.
Jožko Vajda.
The spell of Jožko Vajda is the deadliest of them all.
They say that Meky Žbirka has drilled it,
so he could kill his enemies.
But that's just a superstition.
Since we all know,
that Meky is a singer with a heart of gold.
and he would never hurt even a fly.
Drevo,
You have such a beautiful face.
[Richard Müller - Po schodoch]
Who would've thought, that
when you poke a screwdriver in your foot corn,
seven more sprout right next to it.
Then I tried an angle grinder, but-
Shut up already, Peder.
I'm especially tired of the daily insults, also today.
I don't look like a rocker at all, except for-
Shut the fuck up, Kim.
Move over, move over!
Move, redhead!
Tooth.
Do your gums bleed when you eat?
Come to my office, I have some Sensodyne there.
Get the fuck out,
you dirty minorities.
This is a mistake of our immigration policy,
pests like this coming to our picturesque Slovakia.
Finally I tried to burn it
above a gas stove,
but half of my foot went up in flames and...
[Geri Halliwell - It's Raining Men]
Jurko, Šlota was joking,
You can join the tournament even if you're black.
Okay, okay.
You Gypsy.
Šaňo, just don't steal the bowl.
Hey.
Gypsy, Gypsy, Gypsy.
Gyppy.
It's a shame that redheads can't participate in the tournament.
Our family has been listening to Žbirka for several decades.
Really? I hate him.
We're joining the tournament!
We will fuck the system over!
Give me five!
We put peroxide in there,
black hair dye
and engine oil.
It won't work...
Well, well, who is talking here?
You tranny!
That white line around
prevents entrance to people like you.
That is, to stupid redheads.
You rocker.
Just so you know,
the fact that I fell on a rake
was an unfortunate coincidence
and inside I am still
Rocker.
a fragile and tender girl,
despite my voice.
But we don't care about that at all.
Because you have a voice like a gorilla.
To winning the tournament.
Bye.
Hop.
It worked, right?
We are the champions!
My friend!
Whoop!
We got in the tournament!
Out of here you redheads, out of the tournament!
What happened?
I don't want to be an old dickhead.
This is your fault!
You fucked up!
Your mother is a whore!
I slept with your mother last night.
You'll call that off, you son of a bitch.
Fight! Fight!
The redheads are fighting!
Fuck him up!
Ctibor is an ugly witch,
Punch your brother, he's a bitch!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Quiet! Gábor is coming.
Bright, sight, height, highlight
Paľko, be quiet already.
[Bikini - Közeli helyeken]
♪ (In nearby places,) ♪
♪ (on top of hills, on top of mountains,) ♪
♪ (in excavated quarries.) ♪
Maroš, puke somewhere else!
Maroš!
Please sit down already
and take away that pig which threw up.
I welcome you all to the selection of three contestants
for the tournament of Meky Žbirka.
I will now dim the lights.
with a sexy move that I learned over the weekend.
Unfortunately, Meky could not come today.
Therefore, the selection will be carried out
using a special telephone connection.
Hello, it's Meky Žbirka.
Sorry I didn't show up today,
but something came up.
So let's get started.
The first contestant is:
37 centimeters.
Well, I think that makes it obvious.
[Rytmus - AKM]
Number two!
Well, there's some semen here...
The biggest whore.
[Projekt Vandal - Špinavá kurva]
And number three:
The last contestant is
Fucking Gypsy!
Hope you die, gyppy!
He is a black gypsy.
Excellent!
Women straight to bed because next up
there is an all-male party
topless, which I have organized myself.
But just before, let us introduce you to another price.
from our sponsor -
bankrupt Poltár glassworks.
Poltár decorative trough!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.83,0:33:21.57,Default,,0,0,0,,
A small concert.
White flower...
I am going to buy a kilo of bread.
Cold white flower...
Hello.
Justin Timberlake.
Doctor Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
He shat himself yesterday.
Who shat himself?
Who shat himself yesterday?
That idiot always has shit in his pants, it's gotta be him.
Where did Maroš disappear?
Me?
The day before yesterday.
Who has crapped himself?!
Dano!
You shat yourself yesterday.
You literally shit...
...all over the duvet.
So if someone shits himself, they get automatically chosen for the tournament?
He fucked his way into the tournament.
The old man tore up his anus again.
He gave head 500 times to Old Jano.
That's really not okay.
This is not the Paralympics.
A wretching fraud.
I want to join the tournament too,
I'll shit myself as well.
Fuck, you cannot be serious.
There's shit all around, everywhere around.
This is going to be a huge embarrassment for Hogwarts.
(Is he really not ashamed?)
You fucked up.
(What a pig...)
(If Hitler was still alive,)
(he would not tolerate this.)
[AC/DC – Highway to Hell]
I would send him to work in...
...disgusting Hungarians.
Drevo, did you sleep with Žbirka because of the tournament?
One man in his seventies isn't enough for you?
No, I didn't sleep with him!
You're leading me on, you liar!
I don't like Meky at all!
I'm gonna smash my fucking head open on a lamp here.
The invasion from the south has begun.
They want unrest in our ranks.
Then they attack
and restore the model of contemporary Hungary.
I won't allow this!
(I can't listen to this shit...)
(You stinking blind man!)
One more word in that gibberish
and I will cut off your head
and then I'll shit down your throat,
you Mongol!
Stop it, you two!
Vasil, you are in contact with Meky,
it is up to you.
What can be done.
Meky has for some reason
selected four contestants.
This could end up being an embarrassment for Hogwarts,
if it will be
represented a clumsy oaf
who can't even keep his own shit up his ass.
That cannot be,
he dropped another load in his pants.
[Strapo - Prší, prší]
Old Jano,
Isn't this just a show on your part?
Drevo really didn't get there
through your bed?
Unfortunately, not this time.
In that case, he must have fucked over the system, right, Ľudo?
And so he should be punished accordingly.
Žbirka cannot be contacted either.
Rumor has it that Meky had a minor accident in Patince,
but apparently he is fine now.
He tripped over the bathtub, or something.
I don't want to get into this,
but in the fifth psalm of the Quran it says,
that if a man deceives his neighbor,
he should be freed of his sins within three days
by shaving excess pubic hair.
I consider it a duty.
Ľudo!
Are you starting with that again?
Jano,
Tell him something already.
Jozef,
Bring Drevo.
We're going to shave him.
And no slapping black students on the way!
Sure, I understand.
And now, kindly, everyone get out.
I need to jerk off.
Oh, of course, the old dickhead's got full balls again.
Fantasising about this one boy.
I might as well not give a fuck anymore,
I'll break the fucking display cases in the hallway,
Gypsies can then pick them up.
May their black stumps rot.
Cross-eyed bastard.
I wish his mother
would beat the crap out of him.
You have no shame
to cheat like this,
you rotten bastard?
I'm going to poison you with cyanide tonight.
So you drop dead, you fucking, fucked-up turbo dickhead.
Peder, what's wrong with you?
Fraudulent asshole.
So even you now think that I cheated?
This can't be right.
You might even win and get Žbirka's signature.
Me, who knows all of his lyrics by heart,
I will get jack shit.
I don't know why Žbirka chose four contestants,
I didn't blow Old Jano.
and I didn't cheat in any way.
Look.
Last year I canned gooseberries and they boiled over...
...like three jars of them.
I don't want a signature,
only the book We're Making Jam at our Cottage House.
Gooseberries...
[The Doors - The End]
Fuck your gooseberries...
Well, what a quartet this is...
Hungarian,
whore,
Gypsy
and a cross-eyed.
Good evening, good evening,
My name is Vajcomíra Gombitová.
I write for the Nota bene newspaper,
a tabloid newspaper where we twist everything.
That's why it's mainly bought by the homeless.
And your fucking mothers.
I'm going to interrogate you a bit today.
How many beets have these soft lips tasted?
Yo, you whore.
How many condoms already?
Did this Hungarian stallion break?
And how many lice are hiding?
in this dirty gypsy mane?
She has already endured so much racist taunts...
You had to remind yourself.
That's the one with the restless bowel.
So, who will be the first candidate?
I take it as nonverbal.
login.
Smear here.
I'd rather leave it leaning,
let it air out.
[Christina Aguilera - Nasty Naughty Boy]
You have a beautiful face...
Don't you want a blowjob?
Blow-, uh-, who?
You better come down, you rascal.
but you know very well what I'm talking about.
My nipples have been standing for about two weeks now,
until my milk spurts out.
So tell us -
unsemenated Dano Črevo.
Wood.
Yes.
I received some behind-the-scenes information,
It's whispered in the corridors,
that you have a certain close relationship
with the current school principal.
Wouldn't you like to finally try some...
wild...
female?
That's not entirely true.
In fact, I just
He once smoked because he threatened to throw me out of school.
Interesting, Dana Vedro.
Wood
Listen to me, bunny.
I'm sweating terribly from excitement right now,
I'm all wet, even under my armpits.
and it scratches me down there.
Well, maybe you have scabies.
But, where?
Since I overcame vaginal mycosis,
so I have no problems.
Don't write that there, you dick.
SORRY, YOU CUNT.
Look, bunny,
women my age
they have already experienced something.
And indeed,
you could learn something.
You must be fed up by now.
that damned director.
Don't you want to at least suck the bullets?
Hey, wait!
Are we having a conversation here, or are we flirting?
You dirty bitch.
[Owl City - To The Sky]
Dear Mr. Wood,
We regret to inform you that
that the product you ordered, Sirius Black coal,
cannot be delivered to you due to suspicion of
fucking rat poison,
who is that Polish, clumsy supplier
in that poor pharmaceutical hole
fucked up in a vat of coal during the production process.
As a consolation, we are sending a keychain
and a pen with our pharmacy logo.
Hello, is anyone here?
Peter.
Old Jano.
Maros?
Hello.
Finally free...
Nota bene diary.
Gombit's globetrotter:
Damn it,
victim of vaginal mycosis,
whose dick is regularly sucked by the headmaster of Hogwarts,
suffers from severe asexuality.
As was recently discovered-
That journalistic hyena!
[Robo Kazík - A House on a Hill]
Dano Drevo,
My name is Robo Kazík.
Maybe you've heard of me before.
Who?!
Clearly.
Nobody knows the classics anymore today.
It's all Žbirka, Müller, Kotuľa.
I sang hits like:
The Wine Has Not Turned Sour Yet,
Marína, When I Sing Tears Flow,
You'll find me in the Bay.
No, I don't know those.
But I've definitely heard that name somewhere before.
It tells me something.
Remember.
He didn't bite you...
...pes?
Own dog,
when you went to feed him
bit your ear.
And he fucked you around the yard,
I heard.
Pes...
Let's leave it at that.
Let's get to the point.
Miro Žbirka canceled his concert tour of Žitný ostrov
No one has seen him for a long time, he avoids the public
and it is unknown where he is staying.
Maybe he has AIDS.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What are you stuck on?
Listen.
Meky last performed
at the acid manufacturers' convention in Patince.
And after the performance they took him out
some miracle, tangled in arafats,
which howled for the White Flower.
Damn, quiet down there!
Someone is trying to take a nap here.
Fuck, I have to work at six tomorrow, don't worry...
And what does that even mean, Mr. Kazík?
I have one theory,
but first tell me Dana,
Have you ever had skin problems?
I haven't had a single fuck in my life!
So be very careful, because-
So I go to work,
so I can put bread in my mouth
and have something to eat.
Same, Robo.
So I'll have some cute calves here,
What are they doing here at night, wake them up.
Well, that's what I could think.
Hello, Peter.
What were you yelling here?
Robo Kazík appeared to me in the fireplace.
So I talked to him.
You're hallucinating again,
You fucking junkie.
I'll give him Richard Kazík,
stinky dick.
He'll come to his senses,
when he finds his mother's head
cut off in bed, bloody.
Pig.
[Robo Kazík - This solo belongs to us]
Meky Žbirka missing.
Dana, did you know that periodontal disease in dogs
almost always ends with teeth being pulled out?
Then the poor dog lives
without rotten teeth.
That's great, though.
but I don't care at all.
And do you know what herbs are used for
rinsing the dog's muzzle?
Bubák, please, that's enough.
I have to learn.
That's a shame.
But maybe Petra and Kim will be interested in these things.
Listen, Peter, this is total bullshit.
You better fuck off.
So they're coming to the butcher shop, huh?
Especially that pate is a bitch.
Peder made a joke
and he wants me to tell it to you.
So:
Here comes the peas and pate...
...to the butcher's and the butcher says to them:
"Please fuck the pussy."
Pate...
What?!
Wait.
You forgot that pate
fucks with a butcher.
So, the peas are fucking
and pate...
so...
I don't want to have to repeat it to you again.
I have stuff to do, so leave me alone.
That's the biggest piece of shit-
I know, you mangy bastard!
To hell with such an asshole.
[Rhythm - Jebe]
Why am I here with you, Obedient?
Shlota ordered me to show you,
which will be the first discipline in the tournament.
I hope Brigitte doesn't see you.
What Brigitte?
And what's that on your head?
Is that saliva?
It is the sweat of Kazakh pigs.
Hair holds its shape firmly
and they smell nice.
Quick, put on that cloak!
Obedient...
I'm here, you overgrown giraffe.
I hope you didn't eat like I told you.
She didn't eat, but I found it in the kitchen.
rotten pork loin.
I almost couldn't stand it.
I believe it, just the name makes my stomach churn.
You promised we would eat like kings.
So tell me what.
Don't stress me out.
Dragon droppings, Brigitte.
Dragon droppings.
A delicacy!
This is life!
You pig!
May your mother kill you!
Dragons?!
What is that supposed to mean?
Why?
I'll set them on fire at night, they'll burn.
You whores!
I really don't know why Žbirka chose dragons.
This one is called Rastik.
However, his real name is Rastislav Synek.
Son?
Yes, the cousin of the snake you fucked.
In the Chamber of Secrets, right?
Yes.
So I have a problem, don't I?
Fucking dirt, dirty, fucking!
I prefer a black gypsy,
How to smoke a dick in the morning.
What Wood,
Have you already had your morning smoke?
in the office?
You stink of semen, Wood.
Dana, my father died today.
I wouldn't like semen every morning.
Have you felt the lump on Old John's balls yet?
What are you saying?
Listen.
Neuhneme.
Oh, they gave me such a price for those badges,
I took 500 of them.
You stink, Wood.
Can I have a moment, Sano?
No problem, brother.
Don't steal it, you gypsy.
Okay.
Those badges.
Tell me who made them.
There are whispers that it was you.
Do you really want to know?
Well, actually...
ordered them...
Peter
and forced them on me,
to give them away.
He threatened me.
I'll give you a discount for larger purchases.
You can also take it from your mom, your brother.
Go to hell, Gypsy.
I call you Peder,
That little multiplication table isn't that problematic.
Just sit down for an hour a day and it will work.
Badges are going to hell, huh?
You pig.
What are you shaking?
You ordered them anyway.
Well, not me.
So who ordered them?
Sano.
That's stupid.
It fits everyone, everyone.
Dude, I really don't want those badges.
not even with a discount.
Ready for humiliation, Wood?
A cripple like you doesn't stand a chance in the tournament.
I support Šaň Fekete.
Although he is a Roma,
but at least he doesn't get his panties wet.
That the fungus doesn't hurt you,
You fake Nazi!
Support Gypsy!
You are a disgrace!
Of my generation.
(You fucking son of a bitch!)
(NO!)
[The Coasters - Yakety Yak]
So let this come out of your mouth
representative of the proud Nordic race!
What should he think about in his free time?
about re-enacting the Holocaust.
Joseph, what is that?!
What...? Well...
Get out of here, you bastard!
Is that an otter or a porcupine?
Ferret,
You blind pig!
Taste his dick,
fat people.
(Nazi, back!)
(Hungarians are the best!)
Are you going to try your Hungarian on me?!
Jozef! Jozef!
Wait a minute!
Come here!
Jožko, wait!
Hello!
Himmler a Goebbels
they are turning in their graves,
You hypocrite!
Joseph!
I know where you live, you Pharisee!
You are aggressive,
Racism is awakening in you again.
and it pulls you a mile away.
What did you get yourself, Joseph?
Orešanské wine.
You are a dirty scumbag,
You excite me!
Go to hell, you fucking midgets.
So that your mother will kill you.
Wood,
Come with me.
Wealth, what is happening to the world.
The German supports the Gypsy.
[Ján Ambroz - On the King's Staff]
Wood, I knew from the beginning,
that the soul of a nationalist sleeps within you.
What you said to Stan today
It just confirms my assumptions about you.
Just that last name -
Wood - portends
of pure-blooded Slavic ancestors.
Lumberjacks from the Slovak Ore Mountains.
This leg
She's already kicked so many gypsies,
You wouldn't believe it, Dana.
You remind me
me in early childhood -
Young racist!
...tanks.
And we will go and level Budapest!
Don't pay attention to that,
That's just one tanker from Žilina.
Was I wrong, Dana?
Do you have any lumberjacks in your family?
Mama...
smoked once
forest.
I like you.
I like your opinions and thoughts.
And that's why I decided
to help you in the tournament.
You couldn't do it yourself.
For my whole life
I didn't see a person -
so unathletic,
such a log!
Let me tell you something,
No offense Dana,
but my grandmother had
similar movements
after a stroke.
That's why you need to come up with a tactic.
Do you understand, Dana?
So tell me,
What are you good at?
What do you like to do, Dana?
I don't know...
Quite happy
I am writing off water meters.
Well, that's completely up to you.
Then egg roll.
Preparation
and
broom.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
watching the first discipline
Meky Žbirka tournament, in which
... competitors ... must ...
pussy... fucking microphone...
... screw up the whole tournament.
Bets, bets!
The wood falls off in the first ten minutes.
Two to one.
Five euros to screw up.
That's a joke, boy.
Great choice.
It only remains for us to introduce
the last of the dragons.
Please give me a round of applause for
Rastislav Synek!
Fuck that bitch!
The plant is obviously already heated.
That would be a feast for the eyes if
This dragon just fucked up
Dana Dreva.
Damage!
Damage.
Do you know who I am?
Müller?
NO,
That's Kim.
Not Richard.
I bet 15 euros.
To your death.
Come say goodbye.
What do we have here?
A young romance between
Given by Jebom
a...
metalist.
Tell our readers,
how many times during anal intercourse
you uncontrollably
Did the stool explode?
Tell me.
Be quiet!
You're not a good journalist!
Love to flourish
in all genders.
It's for me.
I was waiting.
a slightly different voice.
It doesn't matter, you have it anyway.
other advantages than vocal cords, right?
Good news!
Every competitor,
who survives today
will receive a gift certificate from
Komárno secondhand shop Gizela.
They have overalls, leggings.
What are you doing here, boy?
Nothing.
Fucked up lip.
Blind.
Vasil, losovanie.
Well, so.
We will create such an ellipse.
The girl will go here.
Then the Hungarian will go second.
And this is the last one.
As you wish.
Slovak folk dragon
Complain.
He is looking for food.
in settlements in eastern Slovakia.
Latin dragon
Kokoticius.
American dragon
Kokotovich.
So that remains -
A plant.
What are you talking about?!
Nothing.
Rastislav Synek.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:35.94,0:56:39.30,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:56:37.70,0:56:39.70,Default,,0,0,0,,
So you finished it, brother.
Your task is to get
golden egg,
in which there is a riddle
by Meky Žbirka.
You must solve this puzzle.
to solve,
otherwise you will not advance to the next round.
Competitors,
who will not survive
and the dragon will not eat him,
will be thrown
ravens as food.
I hope that
Mr. Wood will remember that.
The janitor is already here today.
he was drinking, but he was supposed to start in 10 minutes
So, come on, Sano.
Gypsy! Gypsy!
And the last contestant,
Tailed Gabor,
He defeated his dragon and gained...
But, but what are we seeing?
Gábor takes off his sweatpants
and strikes the tired dragon
Your dick in the ass!
Incredible, incredible!
Ladies and gentlemen. But now...
Let's go to the black sheep of the tournament,
Let's welcome the dirty liar
Dana Dreva!
They won't leave me alone here again,
in this cesspool.
You lousy bastard.
Here's some worm for me.
They threw a snotty one.
I have to get back together with him.
I don't do anything to anyone,
I would rather go to a bar.
Oh my God!
[Kevin MacLeod - Truth of the Legend]
You fucked my cousin.
What are you doing?
You pig!
You will lie here, here.
Ty Pankhart laughed.
I won't drag on here.
with this sweltering twilight.
Oh my God!
To kill with a knife or tail.
or mother.
How the poor chatterbox is struggling.
God!
So I was supposed to have lunch at home
and instead
I will eat the stinking nit.
Where the fuck are you going?!
It's bouncing off my face.
This is annoying me.
Use a broom, Dana!
Use a broom!
Don't advise me, you cunt!
Where are you running to?
You squinty rudder.
Here, I'll hide behind the stones.
Come here!
Jesus Mary.
That he can't die from this.
So he'll walk around here every stone.
Where are you staring at?!
Well, you finally came out.
from there.
So is this possible?!
Tak on mi tu na metle uleti.
Wait, wait!
You'll all laugh, I'm 62 years old.
But you'll laugh.
I broke the chains.
Even that broom won't help you anymore.
You nit!
I'll fuck your god.
Delegates are fucked.
You're going!
You're going, Rastya!
Well, this is a hard-working dick.
Old, but he hasn't seen this before.
For such a shit to fly on a broom.
[Audiomachine - Guardians at the Gate]
I'll load my gun again.
here on the walls.
You idiot!
I can fuck off about that,
I'm going to try something else on him.
Well, look at him!
That he can't die from this.
You pig!
Well, look, look.
How is it that they grab onto that roof?
those poor stumps.
Well, I already have you,
you herbra bitch
Oh my God, I'm going to kill myself here on these tiles.
Come on!
Come here!
Both!
But the world has not seen this yet.
Cabinet!
But fuck your motherfucking motherfucker.
Tails when he wants and dicks.
But hey, he can't die.
His ass is burning, you bastard.
Don't run away from me, you Mahagar whore!
I've had enough,
This is how I keep having to work hard for you.
I fuck the wing and it fucks up.
Don't mess with that gongala, for God's sake.
He fucked me up a lot.
I fucked up my nose.
Maroš, don't be shy here,
You are lying on my hand.
I bled out all over, bitch.
I fucked him!
[Tim McMorris - Life is Beautiful]
Just kill the dragon
and popularity is back.
We are dirt.
Human waste.
Be quiet already!
Here you go, Dana.
Are any of my people here?
Yes!
NO.
Should I open it?
Yes!
NO!
[Justin Bieber - Baby]
What are you, a nerd?
That you listen to Bieber.
Okay people, this is going to be a long one.
Pretend you're not listening to them.
Hi.
Dana, I don't have any money.
I fucked everything up on scratch cards.
Come on, talk.
What do you want?
That voucher for the secondhand store.
I also asked other contestants,
but they donated them to the foundation for
hunchbacked blind men.
Okay,
and why should I give it to you?
Because we're friends, right?
You fucked me up this morning!
What?
It wasn't me!
Dana, listen to me now.
I have a doppelganger at school,
It's called the Dnieper,
looks exactly like me,
he even has a similar voice.
That's it.
He was elbowed in the temple.
I am you
supported the whole time.
That's it.
poured into liquid soap.
That wasn't me.
Peter, you are
so rude,
until it makes me physically sick.
That's what everyone tells me.
Well, at least now
I don't have lice.
Peter...
[John Frusciante - This Cold]
Hello, Esmeralda,
How much did they give you in that collection?
Twenty-nine crowns, sea.
Look what hours it is!
The golden hour, the sea.
Hey Dig, let's get him going.
The crippled one,
how can he not drink?
That's a dick.
What has polio?
Fucked.
That's probably not true.
I can fuck off about that.
Before the dragon's discipline
attacked a contestant backstage
Dana Wood
Crazy computer scientist?!
The couple got married
sexual harassment
in front of surprised witnesses.
A new bachelor couple at Hogwarts?
Not only did you get me again
they got involved with a man,
They're still putting me together.
with such a loser.
Fucking life!
I'm going to cut my wrists again.
A shipment for you, Peder.
Thank you, Adam.
What is that?
Go to hell!
You didn't take your medicine again.
He has Tourette's syndrome.
and sometimes has seizures.
This is from a secondhand store in Komárno.
What the fuck...
What the hell is this supposed to be...
What is this supposed to be?
That's you.
They're kidding, Peder.
And look at this.
Don't catch me,
You shit.
Ctibor, this is more disgusting.
than your face.
But at least I won't be dancing in it!
What's funny?
These are
Mongolian ceremonial robes!
You're going to be a dick!
And that dance is...
mandatory?
Traditional Hogwarts Ball
will take place this year on February 30th.
Today we will learn
three basic steps.
Don't look there.
like fuck.
The ball will be opened by the popular, ageless,
60-year-old teenager
Sisa Sklovská.
He also confirmed his participation.
former moneylender
Boris Kollar,
so instead of canapes
will be served
contraception.
Despite the efforts of our professor
Jozef Šlota,
I was afraid they would be able to
to participate in the minority,
I am Arabi,
women,
black people,
ľudoopi,
and after installation
cameras in the main hall,
to prevent theft,
also Gypsies.
Well, I'll take a baton and a stun gun!
Kotleb on them!
We'll call the Nazis!
Heil Hitler!
Calm down!
I would like to warn all the ladies,
to be careful before the ball
for personal hygiene.
Shave your armpits,
fusion,
wipe your ass
and above all, take care,
Don't let your mouth stink.
as if you were eaten
two-week hiatus.
I heard you say to her
The esophagus or tonsil is rotting.
So what's rotting, her esophagus or her tonsils?
Her whole throat is rotting.
The whole thing is falling apart.
Your partner needs to breathe!
And obese girls,
You don't have to be ashamed!
Smart dress
They'll cover your fucking hams.
On Uršulin's hill
could be fried
even from three months.
I see that Mr. Peder
He has a mouth full of words.
Come to me.
What?
Vztyk, you pankhart!
I recommend you,
so you can hold your breath now.
Please?
My throat is rotting.
So one hand here...
Casanova!
[Bee Gees - Stayin' Alive]
One, two, three...
two, two, three...
three, two, three...
That one probably today
He won't eat, will he?
It won't.
Come on, let's go dancing!
Boys,
if you don't have enough courage,
so stand up and ask yourself
A little cocaine from the janitor.
What the fuck is wrong with him?
He's blown up like a bomb.
He overdosed.
Look how snow is falling from his nose.
How was I supposed to know I would get
diarrhea,
just before
old bastards?
Dana, I've never seen anything more disgusting.
Piglet...
Humus.
Those were
Kilos of liquid shit, Dana.
Rolling down the stairs.
Well, what?
I was so overwhelmed.
That's a piece of stinky cock.
Get away from this, keep shitting, it's disgusting.
Pus from fuckers.
So I came up with this completely by accident at the time,
when I didn't wash myself
even from three weeks,
so on the chest
I developed a huge rash.
and when I was squeezing it out with pliers,
So everything just fell apart for me.
I love the lice on your beard.
Well, and then...
I was hospitalized.
There were some bacteria in that rash.
Well, what about you?
and gastronomy?
♪ (There's a big fire in the system, a big flame.) ♪
[Heroes - Speak Up]
♪ (When the rhythm plays, the style sticks to the drum.) ♪
♪ (Those who didn't grow up with it can't understand it.) ♪
♪ (I wonder why these guys have been doing this for years.) ♪
♪ (So let everyone who dares shout and join us:) ♪
♪ (Up with the word, up with the word, up with the word always!) ♪
You're shaking your ass, Misho,
She has the most disgusting hair.
Kolman, already
His gray hair is starting to grow.
But no one has that
A fat slut like this Kim.
That's more oil than
from Sunday duck.
Peder, this childish one of yours
Humor can't distract me anymore.
You're still awful.
Watch how
the slave girl gains.
What is it?
What?
Ty...
for five crowns
you will plow
in my field.
For five crowns?
Okay.
Kim?
Listen.
You wouldn't want to
to dig?
Kim, what about you?
You have no future at all.
I'm just looking at you.
You'd better come and plow.
Peder, I've had enough of these insults from you.
You immature scumbag!
You primitive!
That's a dirty abortion,
I cut it with a kitchen knife, a rusty one.
What's wrong with her?
I don't know, maybe he has some stuff.
She should finally realize,
that with that voice, doors everywhere are closed.
I wonder if with such a manly woman
someone is going to the ball.
Just some hummus.
Or a desperado.
Hold the pussy.
[Psy - Gentleman]
Hiroshima.
Pokémon.
Up, up, grandpa gangman style.
Clearly.
So-, bye.
Listen!
Yes?
Our Doberman died.
A...
Our Doberman passed away and
I would need to know a recipe.
I don't understand.
Repeat.
I would need to know...
some recipe for a dog
from you as an Asian.
Damage.
You very...
superficial.
Our culture,
that's not eating dogs
a transvestity.
Other things...
Budha,
mysteriously,
ping pong.
Okay.
Well, nothing then.
That Doberman
so we throw it in the trash.
Sorry.
Damage!
Soy sauce
and ginger.
Dude, drugs are not the solution.
Look, your veins are pierced like
diabetic on infusions.
What happened?
He took a double dose of heroin.
Herak?
Do you have any more?
You definitely still have it.
You don't have one?
None with me
He doesn't want to go to the ball.
I'm a complete loser.
Almost bigger than Dano.
Only the biggest waste remains,
like Uršula or Ctibor.
Peder, I'm standing.
behind you, if you haven't noticed.
What about Gypsies?
Esmeralda?
And Winnetou?
If we go to the ball with the Cigoškas,
We will be laughing for the rest of our lives.
They'll even fuck us.
Good morning!
watches, chains
scooters, gold teeth,
we will get jaundice
at the first three steps of the waltz.
What are we going to do, Dana?
We can't be without a partner,
We'll be like two cats.
We can fuck each other.
Hello!
[Warren Vache - I Can't Get Started]
Grcâm.
Fuck you.
I don't know about you, but I'm going to eat like a pig today.
Cunt.
Fucking robes.
Fuck Hungarian secondhand goods.
I look like...
Fucking Mongol.
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
What are you staring at?!
What are you staring at, you little thing?!
What kind of fluff?
Look at me!
Look what I
They sent those Hungarian whores.
Quite it
it smells...
Where was it?
Maybe in some...
zatuchnutom...
in the Yugoslav warehouse.
I smell like a skunk.
And I'm dancing with a gypsy.
Fuck that.
Damage,
especially watch out for theirs
brownish stumps.
You don't even know it and you're robbed.
What are you shaking about?
Those beggars fucked up
three kilometers of copper wire
from the ground floor last week.
Who are you talking about, what are you talking about?
But Winnetou and Esmeralda,
those two gypsies we dance with.
I didn't wear any jewelry just to be safe.
Late, young man.
And you don't have a chain?
I don't have one.
Don't you have one?
Gypsy dirt...
Silverware disappeared from the main hall,
Don't you know anything about it?
Silverware?
What are you deaf for?
Anyway,
Professor Jozef Šlota
wants to release at the ceremonial entrance
Nazi recruitment chant.
Are you okay with that?
Yes.
Excellent.
And where are you coming from?
From the Fiľakovo fair?
You smell like an old sausage.
I was looking for you.
Haven't you seen a silver one somewhere...
But I don't like sausage!
Come on, you black idiot.
That Doberman you helped...
I just want to let you know,
that you will eat with your hands.
Someone screwed up the cutlery.
[Rhythm - Gold Diggers]
That's a prostitute, mother!
You too.
(Hello, boy.)
♪ (Our flag flies before us.) ♪
[Forward! Forward!]
♪ (We're going into the future for each other.) ♪
♪ (We march for Hitler,) ♪
♪ (through the night and through the pain,) ♪
♪ (under the banner of youth,) ♪
♪ (for freedom and bread.) ♪
♪ (Our flag flies before us,) ♪
Who is Gábor fucking with?
♪ (Our flag represents a new era.) ♪
Some...
transvestite.
♪ (And the flag leads us to eternity!) ♪
Eva Máziková, maybe.
♪ (Yes, the flag is more than death!) ♪
Well done, very well done!
Repeat, repeat!
Well, now we'll go like this.
[Yolanda Be Cool & DCUP - We No Speak Americano]
Grab my ass, you scumbag.
For the ass?!
Maroš, you sick bastard!
Hey, Slovaks,
still ours
Slovak
speech lives.
[Zone A - Bread]
Put me down, you whores!
Look at her.
With a Hungarian!
She still did better than the two of us.
Will you blow me off, beauty?
Oh, I'll suck you off.
Down to the root!
Thank you very much,
We'll have our latest hit in a moment,
Fucking dick in a whore.
Gabor...
(Why are you wearing women's clothes?)
Still just clothes.
Gabor keeps asking me,
Why am I wearing a dress today?
You're a really fucked up bitch for not understanding this,
you fucking.
Peder, what are you talking about?
The bitch doesn't understand.
Gabor thinks you're a boy.
Boy?
How could this have occurred to you?
I spent hours applying makeup, going to the hairdresser.
I did everything to make it shine out of me.
the purest...
femininity.
And even through that, he thinks,
that you have a dick.
And two poached eggs!
Don't you have a euro for bread?
I don't have one.
Red-bellied sea bream, sea.
When I say this in the village...
[Tenacious D - Fuck You Gently]
Peder, realize!
Nobody thinks I'm a boy.
I have breasts!
Please...
those two hills.
Please?!
Why would Gábor want a boy?
Because he's bisexual.
And how did you come up with that?
Everyone knows that, you bitch.
Peder, stop insulting me so much!
I have to listen to it every day.
I'm reaching for my life!
Calm down, you fucking witch.
You're splashing around here.
like a raging bitch.
Damage.
What are you doing hanging around here?
He was squinting.
You're lost, you idiot.
Get out of here!
She won't sit down for a week,
when Gábor blows her anus.
I'll drown you in shit!
You little bastard! Get down!
Harpy insane.
Look how crazy he is, get out of here.
Hands up!
Sorry.
We'll see how it goes.
I'm completely involved at this point.
Is it your name?
[Miro Žbirka - What hurts, will heal]
Mr. Zbirka,
They don't understand the riddle in the egg at all.
And besides,
their skin condition is constantly worsening.
Well, you know, Mr. Žbirka, that's puberty.
I won't accept any grumpy faces.
before the release of my album.
Well, what if we pushed them
chamomile?
But it's great for the skin.
Well, chamomile would work.
Damage!
You're sweating somehow,
This is not good for the skin.
If you get fucked over by this,
So don't wish for me.
What, you sweaty dick?
Do you know who fucked me?
Ctibor!
We also had a little fun.
Fet is the way!
Hi.
[Grimaso, Separ, Hector - Hnus]
So how is it going with Pedro?
Are you friends again?
At first I ignored him and was pissed.
I wanted to kill myself.
When I already had the noose around my neck,
So the bastard came in and gave me a coloring book.
Which said "Sorry".
I have to tell you something.
I started taking male hormones,
I will become Stefan.
What are you shaking, Kim?
Dana, what if I'm the only one who doesn't see it?
What if it really is my destiny to be a man?
Damage.
Maybe my voice will get thicker.
They will shave their backs, their mustaches will grow.
I'm going to need support, Dana.
Wood!
Wood, hey Wood!
What about Meky's riddle?
[Francesco D'Andrea - Gypsy]
You already solved it.
egg?
Fuck you.
Listen, we figured it out in the settlement.
I'll sell you the solution for five liters.
I don't have that much.
Stick it in your ass, you Cigoš,
I want three... thousand.
And you can pay me in gold too,
paintings, antiques.
Infuse beetroot in chamomile.
No to
I also take iron,
copper cables, car batteries.
Romano hip hop...
[Kevin MacLeod - Long Stroll]
Infuse beetroot in chamomile.
What now, you charlatan?
Open it in the water, you dickhead!
In the harmonica!
Fucker!
And get dressed, you dick!
So, underwater, that is.
Danö!
Did you notice that I'm half
bodies submerged in shit?
I'm thinking,
How many of them are there?
yours!
The toilets haven't flushed for a week.
I heard that students
kadia from the windows.
It all falls on the yard.
And there he collects the shit in a bucket
some Indian student.
Leave me alone.
I have a job and I'm completely naked.
So let's take a look at the pipik!
What the fuck is that little zucchini?
That's a real shame.
Did I notice correctly, Dana?
Is there any?
gentian behind the foreskin?
But yeah, Dana.
Be more talkative.
What are you doing with that egg?
Are you completely fed up with this shit?
Hello, this is Meky Žbirka.
[Miro Žbirka - The Wall of Our Love]
I see your face is sunken
in chamomile water, so
you advance to the next round.
There you will have your face exposed to cold water,
so find a way to get in there
stay submerged for ten minutes.
And rub some oil on your face.
Try a face mask.
Dry your skin every day before bed.
Pony, pony.
Kuc.
Hi.
You can take a break,
you transparent bitch?
But...
Such a harsh dictionary
from such a skinny guy
a beggar.
You have a figure like
A Jew a week before his death
and your body is white as if you
was the owner of a lime kiln.
Damage...
And your zucchini...
I'm already starting to feel the first symptoms of hormones.
Kim, nobody's yours
They don't care about the past.
The worst are the legs,
they get hairy quickly.
This is like punishment with this bitch.
I shaved them today.
And the manure completely clogged the drain.
Are you completely fucked?!
I'm supposed to die in the water tomorrow.
and you're dealing with enlarged clitoris here.
Dana, I need support!
I will commit suicide if people ignore me.
Leave me alone, you dick.
Honor the work!
On the first floor it is just beginning
racist fair.
I'd be happy to take you there.
Professor, but we just
we are taking on the challenging feeling of my...
Shut up, you hermaphrodite.
We just pacified
one brown pussy
with a bucket of shit.
So we pour it on him and then we burn him.
You're coming with me.
Wood, you stay here.
Bug.
Tell Drev about yours.
meth trip in eastern Slovakia.
What the fuck? The best smažka in Stropkov.
In the cultural center.
We were small
pico from Cinkot's dealer.
I poured it into my snout like
fuck at a techno party.
Those were crystals,
I almost...
The nasal septum was fucked up.
Bug!
Me at all,
but it doesn't interest anyone at all
pico from Cinco's dealer,
nor how you danced in a frenzy
s kurvami
in Stropkov.
I have a few hours to find out.
How to survive 10 minutes underwater.
I'll probably get it tomorrow.
He's really fat.
I'll give you some weed.
Three to one that Drevo will be last.
Tutovka.
Four to one that he will drown.
One to two, that Ctibor
she will remain a virgin forever.
May your mother kill you!
Eight to one that the mother will kill us.
This will fuck you up so bad you won't be able to breathe for 10 minutes.
Symptoms like classic grass.
But there is one problem.
What's the problem?
Well, I've already hidden this grass
long ago in the kitchen with spices
and I don't know if I took it correctly.
What are you talking about, you junkie?!
What did you give me?
Well, you know, I'm still a beginner drug addict.
Well, I hope you weren't mistaken.
You'll have me on your conscience.
Why are you jumping around so nervously, anyway?
I need to shit.
Fuck Maroš!
What the hell are you doing with those cables?
In today's discipline, the competitors are
from right to left: Zuzana de Merde,
next Gábor Székesfehérvár Balaton Szabadi Sóstó
behind him is Sándor Fekete
Eat it!
and the last one is Dandy Wood.
Each competitor must free
a person of low value
who finds himself in the middle of this
Ipeľský pond.
Good luck!
You Woodman!
[Miro Žbirka - Atlantis]
Membranes...
Hymens...
To pojeb.
Where are your parents from?
They are both from Cameroon.
Curve!
Add some oregano!
Which direction?
is the level?
Must.
Carp
fucked up.
Where did I get this?
Into some cesspool,
where the Gypsies of Ipelė
kittens drown.
Kukaj
What the fuck is he like?
bubble muzzle.
What?!
Ariel
mermaid
fucked up.
According to the latest information
the French bitch failed
to succeed in the discipline.
The dead body of a prostitute's sister
will be buried tomorrow at 1:00 p.m.
at the school cesspool.
You are all warmly welcome.
What is it again?
Žbirka invented it.
One guy from Spišská Nová Ves
I remember well,
who once shouted at us.
Who came after us
and says: "You promised,
that it will be intimate.
And it's just so small."
Hen, there are some
inflatable Anče
in the distance.
Get up!
Get up.
He wanted to hang himself.
and you put the loop wrong.
Cretin.
Look what a watch I stole.
Beautiful.
Seriously, brother.
You were smoking!
I had nothing!
Eyes like a welder
after night shift!
Let's get moving!
Come on, let's move, let's move the fuck.
Let's get moving.
Dialogue: 0,1:35:20.99,1:35:21.99,Default,,0,0,0,,
He scared me, that one.
Balaton salmon.
What is this bitch hatching here?
I won't let her rot here, though.
I'll take it, I'll be a hero.
Sandor Fekete successfully
It's discipline, my friends!
Congratulations on his Chinese catch too!
Let's go down, Vasil.
And he ends up in second place.
Tailed Gabor.
About the fucking sister
still no rumor or hearing.
It is already rotting at the bottom of the stream,
but what else did she deserve,
Let's be honest.
Krišpin Valley!
Such fat pigs
I'm having a hard time choosing here.
from muddy water!
What's pulling my leg?!
Lake squid!
Fucked up bitches!
Whores!
Well, that's a twist, friends.
It looks like he didn't manage the discipline.
Janos Drevos.
His body will not be fished out,
because this special student
was never popular
and no one would come to his funeral anyway.
Fuck Žbirka!
Danko!
My darling, you are alive!
You need to be undressed.
and inspect the wounds, wait!
He is wounded!
He needs to take his clothes off!
Ty!
You saved my sister.
Anything:
anal, oral, fecal, sadomasochism.
Also prostate massage.
And you deserve it too.
No...
Such an anal would sting...
Come on, let's go get an enema, nurse.
Stone.
Damage!
You look terrible.
As always. Phew!
What were you doing there for so long, Dana?
Lake squid.
You're crazy, Dana!
You're crazy, you fucking junkie.
(Gábor, he will win us everything,)
(be careful, or you will lose.)
(Go Gábor, go winner!)
Let's calm down!
(Always be nice to him.)
(Gábor is our winner! Gábor is our winner!)
Silence!
(Go on, Gabor! Go on, Gabor!)
Sano Fekete wins!
Given the detailed analysis of Jozef Šlota,
who is the video referee for this discipline,
it was found that
Gábor's penis stopped in the water
and thus exceeded the maximum river quotas.
Gabor is therefore
from this discipline
disqualified.
Disqualified!
Racist!
Well, the hard life of people
with a big penis.
You're lucky you have
such a little dick Dano.
Otherwise you would also be disqualified.
Nine centimeters, right?
Hello.
That's a shame.
Heartfelt congratulations, son.
You are very brave.
Fearless.
Now it follows
such a small thing.
Every competitor
He will have a drug test today.
But you don't have to worry, son.
You look like you don't even know,
What is marijuana?
Every drug addict will
of course disqualified.
Vasil!
I celebrated a little yesterday.
alone with myself,
I treated myself to a bottle of plum brandy.
Well, now I should go teach,
So come and tell me if I'm pulling it off.
God! So this is what he can teach.
It stretches for kilometers.
Just don't fuck around, you dirty Russian!
What is this supposed to be, drug tests?
I was sniffing the first league.
I crushed moldy plaster
with cheap coke
and I gave it my all
to decagrams into the snout.
That usually fucked me up for half a day.
So when Dano asked me if I would
He could pacify that Russian,
I didn't hesitate for a second.
Already Dana?
Yes.
[The Red Army Choir - Kalinka]
That is absolutely unheard of!
What is Žbirka doing?!
He will organize a concert.
also the album launch
and with us about the tournament
does not communicate at all.
And into all of that
Vasil gets lost.
The contestants will start to have questions.
Especially that bespectacled bitch
still has some questions.
I don't like to jump into this, gentlemen.
but that squinty guy is eavesdropping on us here.
Damage!
[Blue & Elton John - Sorry Seems to Be the Hardest Word]
We were just mentioning you.
I'll buy the lenses if you don't mind-
Nonsense, you know how to like it.
I'm spraying on those glasses, Dano.
I like this inspector a little bit.
to air out the poop,
but I'll be back in a moment.
For now, offer yourselves as Homošlerkami.
They are candies.
for the right guys.
And really pull me out while doing it
for that gray hair.
I like it that way.
[Gay girls]
[Red Hot Chili Peppers - Slow Cheetah]
Old Jano?!
Janko, I can't sit still after yesterday.
Good job!
Glad it happened.
Dusan, where are you?
Did he put that cream on his ass?
The court summons Istvána Farkasa.
Former director
Rožňava reformatory.
Convicted of Hungarianism
and sentenced to 12 years in prison.
Rožňava reformatory
it was home to many young criminals.
In case of information,
which can be used to catch them
the court will consider your release.
Stephen Farkas,
Are you willing to provide the court with names and evidence?
Again.
Bela Cluj-Napoca
secretly recruited
young men into battle
against Slovakia.
Béla committed suicide.
This information is absolutely irrelevant.
That suicide...
(Fuck you Bengal tiger)
(with his striped cock.)
(I would have preferred to stay in Hungary my whole life...)
Please?
One boy participated
for distribution
child pornography materials.
There are.
Unless there is a name,
so we can end it right away.
Arpad Mosonmagyar.
Old Jánoš will testify to this,
he bought cassettes from him himself.
Your Honor, I must respond to these
the vile lies that are being told here
this ill-mannered southerner brandishes.
Meno Arpad Mosonmagyar
It tells me absolutely nothing.
and I have nothing to do with child pornography
You licked his dick yourself,
and I never have.
You old bastard.
I see you can't control yourself.
So I have to end this process.
(No, no...)
There was still one.
The worst bet.
And?
He's a big fan of Meky Žbirek.
He couldn't understand why Mecca
sings with Marika Gombitová,
why not with him.
So Marike removed the brakes from the car
and she had that accident that left her paralyzed.
Her own nephew.
Jergus
Gombit.
[Marika Gombitová - Confession]
I did it out of love for Meky.
Golden Nightingale 1982.
White flower
the last one is gone.
So how much?
Life imprisonment.
Arpad's cicula
was completely unique.
He had a sign
over the eggs and just to him
the first hairs started to grow.
I always remember fondly how I
He deflowered a drugged man.
Anyway, I have to go now.
to focus on other things.
Vasil got lost somewhere,
Meky stopped responding completely.
Especially since you've planned a new concert
at Čierny Balog and the album launch.
Next week.
[Nightwork - I'm gay!]
It doesn't make sense, Dana.
The whole tournament is falling apart.
Sir, Jerguš Gombit.
who convicted him of that heinous act.
What's wrong with him now?
How should I know that?
I was at that court.
just because of one young handsome man
to an intern I had a crush on.
Why do you ask?
Sometimes I have dreams like this,
rather, they are nightmares
after which I wake up sweaty
and mostly shitty.
It starts in some stale
a black log cabin, something like
four-star hotel in Rimavská Sobota.
What's important is what's in your heart, not what you look like.
Mr. Žbirka, Mr. Žbirka, did you burn a wart, so how come you're not happy?
I enter a room from which I hear various English words,
so it's clear that Meky Žbirka is there.
I want to hold your hand.
Yesterday.
And there's a Mr. Rat with him there
and especially Jerguš Gombit.
But I can't see Žbirka's face,
I just hear him talking around.
about the Beatles and Paul McCartney.
They often talk about the tournament,
but I always wake up and have to wash the sheets.
Don't know what these dreams might mean?
I often dream again.
about you, Dano.
I don't know what your delusions mean.
But the plastic surgeon, what did he do to me?
anal implants were called
Igor Patkaň, MD.
I don't know if this will help you.
(Miro Žbirka ..., Lajos.)
Wait, Wood, come here.
(That's the idiot who keeps screwing up, just wandering around, always lost, lost)
[Areeb - The beloved of the awwal]
Did you know that every fourth
person in the world is a Muslim?
And there will be more of us.
Super.
Come with me.
Dialogue: 0,1:49:05.97,1:49:10.06,Default,,0,0,0,,
I have something here that you could buy.
This.
Do you know what that is?
Some Arabic shit?
Tears of Afghans
polosirôt.
And just drink a few of them,
or bathe in them
and your body will get...
to its original form.
For serious injuries, they are used
as part of the so-called
The Arab ritual of rebirth.
I'll sell you a bottle for four euros.
I'm not interested!
I am totally
on the topic.
Can you hear?!
I sold 70 liters.
this piece of shit to Meky Žbirka,
ale Šaňo Black
He sucked it all out of me.
Mark my words, Wood.
The great Allah sees it all.
He sees everything and will punish you,
You fucking feast!
Ladies and gentlemen, it begins
our last discipline
Meky Žbirka tournament!
Today as usual
we have a slight technical problem
With his dirty
comes with a gypsy's foot
Brown Roma, Šaňo Black!
Next comes the perfumed hooker
with her overgrown shepherdess,
Zuzana de Merde!
[Los Del Rio - Macarena]
In the company of a former criminal
The gifted Hungarian arrives,
Gábor Székesfehérvár Balaton Free Salt Lake.
And how else, the last one,
together with his drunken boyfriend
Damn it!
Well, I'm sorry.
Kill Jebo!
Jano Jebo, dear.
I would like a big round of applause.
for all competitors!
So be quiet.
Silence!
Welcome to the finals.
Meky Žbirka tournament!
Since our school has always
supported racism,
The first Slovaks will enter the labyrinth.
The Black Šaňo
together with Dan Drev.
Since I almost choked yesterday
his laughter,
who will enter the labyrinth next?
Tailed Gabor!
Dialogue: 0,1:51:21.07,1:51:22.07,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,1:51:21.79,1:51:26.43,Default,,0,0,0,,
And she will be the last to enter the tournament
an absolutely uninteresting gray mouse
Zuzana de Merde.
The winner will be the contestant who
who will be the first to find the maze
Poltara decorative roll
and touches it with his finger.
Contestants, come to me.
Come on!
People are getting lost.
and unexplainable things happen.
Meky Žbirka completely stopped communicating,
which is strange because tomorrow
is to have an album launch and a concert
on the Black Balog.
The tournament can be dangerous
and I have the moral right to end it.
But I have a pussy, it's just starting
Man of the Year live broadcast.
So much happiness
I wish.
Last farewell!
Hold on.
The janitor has been without sleep for two days
He was drunk, but he's fresh and ready now.
start-
What?
Alcohol is a scourge.
[Meky Žbirka - I like it]
Mecca Zbirka.
"Collection"
When I had the opportunity to
s Paul McCartney, Paul McCartney
Paul McCartney talking.
It's been a hard day.
[Parno Graszt - I'm going crazy on the piano]
♪ (I'm going to play the piano.) ♪
♪ (Organ whispers,) ♪
♪ (Gézu's mother ran away.) ♪
♪ (Hey Roma, kids.) ♪
Something's going on.
Light at least a small candle.
Fair play.
♪ (Organ whispers,) ♪
What the fuck?!
Curve.
♪ (Gézu's mother ran away.) ♪
What this is.
♪ (Hey Roma, kids.) ♪
(Beautiful, beautiful, whose eyes are blue,)
(whose eyes are black.)
Yesterday.
White flower.
Songs by Lennon and McCartney.
McCartney, McCartney-
My darling,
please don't take your love away.
Love away.
...love away.
I was in Chicago last time.
What did that boy eat?
It eroded my mucous membrane, naturally.
Phew, that's-
Zuza!
To the hospital!
Follow me.
(Live!)
(Cabinet!)
Go away!
Not!
Fuck Hungarian, dig more.
Leave him alone, he only has forints!
Those are completely up to you.
Leave me alone, brother.
You scum!
You Gypsy!
You fucking idiot!
You fucking dick.
God.
Brown.
Wealth!
You bastard!
Do it right.
Oh my God, shit.
Dana, please, Dana, are you blind?
Can't you see that I'm fucking screwed here?
Do you need bigger glasses, Dana?
Do you need higher diopters?
Curvature diopter.
Do you need bigger glasses, Dana?
Dana, please, these plants are suffocating me here.
Curvature diopter.
Those ashtrays are really not enough for you,
You blind fool?
Dana, please help me.
I'll give you back the 16 euros tomorrow.
What do I owe you? You'll have them on your table tomorrow!
Oh please, Dana,
I will pay it back to you with interest.
Thanks, brother.
Thank you very much.
Not at all.
Listen,
those 16 euros
I don't have Dana now.
That's what I thought.
But I'll give them back to you.
Fact.
Okay.
Let's run, come on!
Are you sure it's the one with the big wheels?
I don't know!
Maybe it's someone else.
Fuck it and take it!
Come on!
It smells like boiled rats here.
We must be on some kind of
Romani cemetery.
Well, it looks like this
in our village in the evening.
This is the Rimavskosobotsky cemetery.
We were here with the class on a field trip.
That's steel.
We will receive 120 crowns for this in the collection.
Fuck now for the harvest!
Cigos.
There are more important things than
scrap metal collection.
You'll call it off.
[Miro Žbirka - Flawless]
Dana, what's going on?
I'll break up with you.
I hate Žbirka's songs.
Paul McCartney.
Who are you, what do you want?
Are you here for the steel?
We can work it out fifty-fifty, right?
Jožo Vajda!
NO!
Igor, throw him there for a moment, there
up, right there, let it hold
on that bone.
And throw me into those tears of Afghan half-orphans,
Igor, let him begin.
Arabic ritual.
I can't wait anymore.
the first concert.
I'll unpack it like old times.
So we're going to the ritual.
Pork
bone.
Gnawed
Ivana Christová.
Hand
plastic surgeon.
Cut off
with a knife
Dirty like your mother.
And now only blood
handsome man,
whose face
will be appropriated.
Surprised by
goulash pot.
And the Arabian ritual of rebirth
can begin.
[Choir of Beirut - Ihmadou Al Rab]
♪ (Give thanks to the Lord, for he is good,) ♪
Everything went so fast for you.
...I was like, I kind of flew away.
♪ (For His mercy endures forever.) ♪
That's one of the few things I remember.
And then I really experienced it firsthand.
I was lying in the hotel.
♪ (Praise the Lord.) ♪
I don't want to go anywhere.
I was tiny, so it was even more special.
♪ (Let those who fear the Lord say:) ♪
You have a great face for radio.
That familiar face.
And so I can finish it.
That was an encrypted message.
♪ (His mercy endures forever.) ♪
♪ (Praise the Lord.) ♪
[Miro Žbirka - White Flower]
What will I use to sign autographs?
Thanks, Igor.
And what do I look like?
Breathtaking.
You disappeared.
nipple.
Extend your hand, Igor.
The new album is coming.
It's time to choose a godfather.
Good evening,
bankrupt celebrities.
I appreciate your interest.
to christen my new album.
But who among you remembered me?
after I fucked up in Patince
into acid?
Which of you
He came to visit me.
when they took me to Rimavská Sobota?
I suffered and you ignored me!
Everyone!
Everyone.
Every one of you.
However, when it comes to the album's release,
so you start rubbing yourself in.
Right, Braňa?
Mira, listen to me.
I sent you a postcard,
where I wished you a speedy recovery.
Nothing came to me, Braňa.
No postcard.
They had to fuck it up.
Gypsy women at the post office in Rimavská Sobota.
I can't think of any other option.
I even wanted you
buy a gift basket
and a small box of chocolates,
but I drank it all.
What about the operation, Meky?
Don't be impatient, Igor.
You know how they say that
Slowly you go.
I'm so glad it was found too
in the ranks of plastic surgeons
my fan.
I like Igor,
You'll need that hand.
Mirko.
Thank you.
Mirko!
Could you also tell me then?
to get a pedicure.
My legs are horrible, just looking at them.
But, I can already see that this
Mr. Donor is starting to get nervous.
He's probably starting to suspect,
that he will be cut off
from the face.
From the first moment you were there for me
dark horse, Dana.
Or as they say in English,
Black horse, of course.
I chose it though
three other competitors,
but I couldn't do it and at the last minute
I had to choose you too.
Well, my instinct was right,
from the first discipline she proved
your skin, it's exceptional.
At first she handled the heat of dragonfire without harm,
then she responded beautifully
for a chamomile bath.
And in the end, it wasn't damaged at all.
after an hour
in an ice pond.
In all this time, Dana,
You haven't grown a single dick!
Thanks to your face
the Slovak scene will experience...
return...
Meky's
A collection.
Stop farting that ammonia,
because my nasopharynx is going to fuck up.
So let's go to the surgery.
Don't lie down, Wood, get up.
Get up!
Decency dictates that
in the presence of the biggest megastar
Slovak pop music
one must bow down.
When a person has stopped the winds,
so it is recommended to lean forward.
You'll see how relieved you'll be.
Apple.
Apple!
Oh my god,
You're going to stink up the whole cemetery.
You are an epileptic!
Well, good that you are.
I don't even own your intestines.
Or a dick.
I heard,
that you have a mini version in your shorts.
I don't have it!
Tomorrow at the concert it will fall
Black Balog.
And all the radio stations will play me.
You don't even know,
how your professors helped me.
It's only thanks to them that I got through.
to the tears of Afghan half-orphans
and the Arab ritual of rebirth.
One professor in particular helped me
right under your nose
and no one noticed.
Nobody.
Enough of the nonsense,
The climax of the evening is coming.
I will cut off your head.
while it's still warm.
Jožko Vajda!
Get packed here, otherwise
I will start singing.
I know you don't like mine.
perfect creation!
Those days,
when I feel
very kindly,
smoked
I would too
McCartney.
We copy the Beatles
forever.
My glory is
unfair.
Enough.
Jožo Vajda!
Jožko Vajda!
Paul McCartney. Paul McCartney.
Paul McCartney lives around the corner.
Ringo Starr is standing in the buffet.
Beatles. Pete Brown.
Eric Clapton. J. Bruce.
George Martin. Phil Collins.
Yesterday.
Red Rose Speedway.
Good chords. Follow me.
I want to hold your hand.
Oh yeah, got a something.
Dialogue: 0,2:08:52.26,2:08:53.26,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dana, we are your dead sponsors.
We always hated you,
but we hated it even more
creation of Meky Žbirek.
That's why we're going to help you escape from here.
Dana, take me back,
May my father pull out my gold teeth.
and sell them to a pawn shop.
Daniel,
We never wanted you.
I had an abortion, but
The doctor fucked him up.
So run, you bastard.
Run!
Come here!
Where is he?!
No!
So ladies and gentlemen,
We have winners here!
The wood there is somehow whining,
Who knows what Šaňo fucked him up with,
that he screams so terribly.
But be careful,
It looks like Šaňo Fekete
he died just like that
lousy dog!
These are my things, ladies and gentlemen!
Those are my things.
Danko.
Don't touch him,
Touch me instead.
NO!
Danko.
Damage.
Love.
Sixteen
euros.
He owed me that
Fucked up gypsy.
I saved up for
operation
eyes.
Danko,
You are so beautiful when you cry.
I love you with all my heart.
The biggest debtor has fallen
at this school.
The whore.
Well, nothing so terrible.
didn't happen.
Let me go, you whores!
Two hundred and twenty euros!
Two hundred and twenty.
I lent it to him.
this week.
Nerev.
Take it positively.
We have one less Gypsy.
God, what are they screaming over there?
I would make a celebration out of it.
Mortgage.
14 children!
I'm in trouble.
Marosi, you are mine!
Are you seriously masturbating here?
You're a fucking necrophiliac.
Headache.
[Martin Kelecsényi - I have to go now]
Well, don't scream so much.
Don't yell so much, Wood!
Nerev.
Sad.
Well, don't scream anymore!
Let's have a drink, Dana, what do you say?
I have a twelve-year-old plum tree here.
I'll pour half a glass, okay?
We could get fucked.
Will you disinfect me?
A wound, please?
This scratch?
When my grandfather was beaten by the Hungarians,
with a cane, those were the blows!
I am very tired.
and my head is spinning.
Fuck you.
And tell me why you don't have
scalped face.
Why?
At!
Let's drink more.
I'm starting to have withdrawal symptoms.
The whole tournament was
one huge fraud.
The Žbirka dug himself up.
into acid
and was looking for a donor for a new face.
He looks even worse than usual.
Fantomas fucked.
It even made his nose hurt.
That thin hair of his is
gone forever.
Meky mentioned that he had been
one of the teachers helped.
Don't know who it could be?
It had to be Kolman.
He also sold him those Arab tears.
It was definitely Kolman.
Coleman?
So it wasn't Kolman.
So who then?
When I think about it,
so you were always quite nice
Mira Žbirku, professor.
Well, I always listen.
thanks for his song.
Your generation doesn't know
what is good music!
Meky knew with one dead guitar
to put on such a show that
Even the walls in the cultural centers got wet!
Damn, where's the booze?!
With a new face and a new image
could Žbirka give a concert?
another twenty years, until ninety!
He needed someone to
will return to prominence again
and I guarantee you,
that it wasn't Kolman.
To make such a plan
it required a strong mind!
Think about it a little, you donkey.
Old Jano behaved
been a bit strange lately.
If only he were the one
the megamind behind this?
Old Jano! Oh Wood.
Open your eyes, you stupid calf.
I planned it all!
I escaped from prison!
I pushed Meky.
in Patince into acid.
I found out information from Kolman
about the ritual of rebirth.
Only thanks to me will Meky return.
back on stage.
That old pervert is starting.
to suspect something.
So that face of yours
I'll cut it off right now.
Well, Mecca.
will have it tonight
a new identity.
Jožko-
I'm going, Danko!
Man, pour him some
Tears in my eyes.
Where is the real Jozef Šlota?
Lick my ass, old man.
Don't read my mind and answer!
I spit on your mother's grave.
I am already an old man,
I can't be so angry!
Where is Slota?!
Listen, cock.
...brothers, they will be lost.
Slovaks will come to life
The Slo-
Good evening.
Is the SNS still in parliament?
SNS? What the fuck is wrong with him?
That's a popper, folks.
So give me a little
Leave it for tonight, Ľuda.
Don't worry, Jožko.
The SNS is still there.
[Miro Žbirka - Handsome Boy]
Who is that?
Give me your little face!
Hands off Danko, you dirty bastard.
Jerguš Gombit, I suspected it.
Meky will release an album even without your face.
Look.
You look.
What did your old idol do to him?
It will be the album of the year, there is also
white flower remix.
Also a duet
with a Paul McCartney lookalike.
I wanted to
prevent.
Take that fool into custody immediately.
He is mentally disturbed.
The time has come, Žbirku,
will sit on the throne!
And you in the electric chair.
Come on, Danko, take off your clothes,
I'll check those scratches for you.
Did Mecca hit you in the area too?
Oh great Allah,
Forgive this lost soul.
Dialogue: 0,2:17:26.04,2:17:27.04,Default,,0,0,0,,
Šaňo Black
he was a simple boy.
He loved dancing, social benefits
and my own sister.
But most of all
he loved borrowed money.
The pain of his loss
will remain forever
in each of us.
Because each of us
Did this Roman owe any money?
To everyone.
Cheers.
Šaňo Black
was a fucking beggar,
who spent shamelessly
our hard-earned money
for toluene and vending machines.
We all know him intimately.
Begging for a euro, two for bread.
Some change for the trip to Ružomberok.
Or alms for a sick mother.
And we are all in good faith
They jumped on these lies.
Whether students or teachers.
Mom, don't bother me, I'm at a funeral.
But such a dick.
For these reasons we decided
Okay, okay...
Cremate Šaň Fekete
and add his body remains
into children's bedding.
He's been screwing us his whole life.
So now we'll have to deal with him.
With my black friend
incredible people left
17344€
and many borrowed items.
Rest in peace,
expensive money,
forinty,
jewelry,
car radios,
pimples,
antiques,
watch,
bodywork,
electronics,
tires,
bicycles,
coolers,
traffic signs,
carburetors,
chains...
Don't chase yourself.
You'll need that seed in a moment.
I know you have now
Money problem, Dana.
Probably everyone has that after Šaň's death.
Hi.
So what do we do about it?
I'm willing to help you, Dana.
I mean financially.
I have a rolled up twenty euro bill.
in the anus, Dana.
Do you want to pull it out?
There are.
I'll continue like this.
I can't continue.
Your seed
I can taste
on multiple levels.
I want to move on.
Heartless bastard.
You requested a transfer.
to another school?
Now listen to me,
you hyena.
As long as I am the director
of this school, so you
all transfers
I'll sweep it off the table.
I swear to you here,
You bastard.
Suck my dick
is your life's destiny.
You are chosen.
You always were.
So, calm down a bit, Dana.
and throw away such
head lice.
You're staying here.
I will be there in five minutes.
in the office only in suspenders.
I don't lock the door.
Fuck one,
that he is transferring to another school.
And so one ended
A special year at Hogwarts.
Gábor looked out for himself while saying goodbye
Kim, and since he always wanted
after fucking a transsexual,
decided...
Kim.
Twenty thousand forints
for the operation.
If it's Stefan, call me.
I will wait.
Hi.
Peder, that day
got the last kisses
of your life.
Bye.
(Fuck you, you son of a bitch.)
To Dano,
he's just being mindless as usual
walked, following the mixture
of different races and ethnicities.
How they falsely promise each other,
that I will write.
And at the same time he thought,
where could that be?
to shit as soon as possible,
because it was coming back to him.
French whores were escorted out
with loud applause.
Twelve of them had no idea,
that they are developing in the womb
little baby.
Gábor didn't know that,
that he is the father of five of them.
Žbirka cancels album launch
and all concerts.
What?
Incredible.
How could I do that?
listen to the scoundrel?
I will never do that again.
Fragile girl, huh?
Never.
But you will support me.
Right, boys?
Those hormones really fucked up your voice.
Damage,
at least you.
Sure, Števko.
Listen.
Who is this Maroš?
That will probably remain a mystery forever.
So that was a year.
The next years at Hogwarts were calmer.
and nothing significant happened.
That is, until the pandemic
mycosis of the feet, which
Three-quarters of the students died.
Meky Žbirka surrendered
his singing career and began
to spin cotton candy on
carousels in Šamorín.
A Given Tree,
This is living proof that
that even an ordinary person,
who can only take a shit,
can become a legend.
Maroš, put the fucking subtitles already!
[Fall Out Boy - I Don't Care]
Titles Dano Drevo and Meky Žbirku Tournament
v0.5.5
by Mravec